（チャイム）
（女子生徒）ねえ 今日さ
帰り どっか寄ってかない？
（携帯電話のバイブ音）
Hey, do you want to go
anywhere on the way home?
（携帯電話のバイブ音）
（女子生徒）
あー 私 ケーキ食べたい
（里見(さとみ)蓮太郎(れんたろう)）
なんだよ こんな時間に
Why are you calling me at this hour?
（天童(てんどう)木更(きさら)）仕事よ 里見くん
We've got a job, Satomi-kun.
防衛省まで来て
Come to the Ministry of Defense.
防衛省？
Ministry of Defense?
♪～
～♪
#02 The Mask of Madness
（蓮太郎）俺たちが
呼び出されたってことは―
Did they call us here because
昨日の件じゃないのか？
of what happened yesterday?
（木更）“とにかく来い”しか
言われてないわ
They just told us to come.
（職員）こちらです
天童民間警備会社様
This way, Tendo Civil Security Agency.
（木更）あっ
（蓮太郎）あ…
木更さん こいつは…
Kisara-san, this is...
これ 東京エリア上位の民警が―
It looks like most of the civil officers
in the Tokyo Area have been called...
ほとんど呼ばれてるんじゃ…
うっ あ…
（伊熊将監(いくましょうげん)）おいおい
最近は ガキまで民警ごっこかよ
Hey, now... Are little kids playing
civil officers these days, too?
用があるなら まず名乗れよ
If you've got something to say,
at least introduce yourself first.
（将監）ああ？
うっ
（木更）里見くん！
Satomi-kun!
（将監）おい ガキ
Hey, brat. If you're a Promoter,
where's your tool?
プロモーターなら
道具はどうした？
道具？
Tool?
（将監）お前のイニシエーターだよ
Your Initiator.
道具…
Tool?
延珠(えんじゅ)を… 道具だと!?
You're calling Enju a tool?!
（三ヶ島(みかじま)）やめたまえ 将監
（将監）あ…
Stop it, Shogen!
三ヶ島さん！
Mikajima-san!
（三ヶ島）私に従えないなら―
If you can't obey me, then leave here right now.
今すぐ ここから出ていけ
（将監）うっ… ヘイヘイ
You got it.
三ヶ島ロイヤルガーター所属
伊熊将監
That's Ikuma Shogen of the Mikajima Royal Guard.
ＩＰ序列は 1584位
His IP Ranking is 1,584.
1000番代…
He's in the thousands?
彼は 世界で20万以上存在する
民警ペアの中で―
He's considered to be in the top
1% of the more than 700,000
上位１％以内に属するわ
civil officer pairs in the world.
ちなみに 里見くんと
延珠ちゃんペアの順位
By the way, you and Enju-chan
rank around 120,000.
12万といくつ…
イニシエーターは優秀なのにねえ…
And yet she's such a brilliant Initiator...
（蓮太郎）ん…
しかし 今 ここに―
So the top class of
東京エリア トップクラスの
民警ペアが集まってんのか…
civil officer pairs from the
Tokyo Area are here right now...
ん？
あれが 伊熊将監の…
That's Ikuma Shogen's...
ん？
“おなか すきました”？
"I'm... hungry..."
なんなんだ…
What the hell?
（ドアが開く音）
ん？
（ドアが閉まる音）
（自衛官）ん？
Oose Future Corporation
空席１か…
So, one absent...
この依頼を辞退する者は
速やかに退席してもらいたい
I'd like for those who will decline
this job to immediately leave.
依頼を聞いたあとでは
断ることはできない
Once you've heard what the job is,
you will not be able to decline.
これより 依頼の説明を行う
The explanation for this job will now begin.
（一同のどよめき）
（聖天子(せいてんし)）ごきげんよう 皆さん
Greetings, everyone.
（蓮太郎）聖天子…
Seitenshi...
東京エリアの統治者が
The ruler of the Tokyo Area...
それに 補佐官
And her advisor,
天童菊之丞(きくのじょう)
Tendo Kikunojo...
両親を失った俺を
引き取ってくれた義父
My adoptive father who took
me in after my parents died.
そして 木更さんの祖父
And Kisara-san's grandfather...
依頼は２つあります
We have two jobs.
１つは 昨日 東京エリアで
感染者を出した
One is the extermination of the
Gastrea that caused the infection
感染源ガストレアの排除
of an individual in the Tokyo Area yesterday.
もう１つは
The other is to bring back the case
within this Gastrea unharmed.
このガストレアの体内に
取り込まれているケースを
無傷で回収すること
Reward
以上です
That is all.
（一同のざわめき）
ケースの中身
聞いてもよろしいですか？
May I ask what's inside the case?
あなたは？
And you are?
（木更）天童民間警備会社
天童木更と申します
I'm Tendo Kisara of the Tendo Civil Security Agency.
あ…
おウワサは聞いております
天童社長
I've heard about you, President Tendo.
しかし プライバシーに当たるので
お答えできません
However, that is private, so I cannot answer.
（木更）
感染源のモデル･スパイダー
The source of infection was a Model Spider.
その程度なら
If that's all it is, our Promoter
could bring it down by himself.
うちのプロモーター１人でも
倒せます
なぜ それを民警トップクラスの
お歴々に依頼するのか
So why are you asking all of these
top class civil officers to do it?
破格の依頼料に見合った危険が―
Perhaps there's something in
the case that's so dangerous,
ケースの中にあるのでは？
it warrants such an extraordinary reward?
それは 知る必要のないことです
That is something you do not need to know.
（蛭子(ひるこ)影胤(かげたね)）フハハハハハ…
（聖天子）誰です？
Who is that?
（影胤）私だ
It is I.
（一同）うわっ
お前は…
You're...
（影胤）フッフッフッフ…
フゥ…
私は蛭子　蛭子影胤という
I am Hiruko. Hiruko Kagetane.
お初にお目にかかるね
I believe this is the first time we've met,
無能な国家元首殿
my lady, the incompetent head of state.
元気だったかい 里見くん
Have you been well, Satomi-kun?
（蓮太郎）
どこから入ってきやがった！
Where the hell did you come in from?!
（影胤）正面から堂々と
I walked right in the front door.
もっとも 寄ってきた
ハエみたいなのは―
Though, I had all the little flies
that tried to approach me killed.
全部 殺させたけどね
紹介しよう
小比奈(こひな) おいで
Let me introduce you...
Kohina, come here.
（蛭子小比奈）はい パパ
（蓮太郎）はっ！ あ…
Yes, Papa.
（小比奈）よいしょっと！
Upsy-daisy.
（蓮太郎）いつから背後に!?
When did she appear behind me?
（小比奈）蛭子小比奈… 10歳
I'm Hiruko Kohina. I'm ten years old.
（影胤）
私のイニシエーターにして 娘だ
She is my Initiator, and my daughter.
（小比奈）パパ あいつ
鉄砲 こっちに向けてるよ
Papa, that guy's pointing his gun this way.
斬っていい？
May I cut him down?
（影胤）よしよし
まだダメだ 我慢なさい
Now, now, not just yet. Be patient.
むう～ パパ
Aww, but, Papa...
（蓮太郎）なんの用だ？
What do you want?
（影胤）私も このレースに
エントリーすることを伝えたくてね
I wanted to announce that I'll
be entering this race, as well.
“七星の遺産”は 我々が頂くと
And that we'll be taking the
Inheritance of the Seven Stars.
七星の遺産？
The Inheritance of the Seven Stars?
（影胤）そう 君らが
探すことになっていた―
Yes, that's what is inside the case
that you were supposed to find.
ケースの中身だよ
（蓮太郎）
それで こいつ あの部屋に…
That's why he was in that room?
（影胤）
ルールの確認をしようじゃないか
Why don't we go over the rules?
私と君たち どちらが先に―
Let's see who can claim the
Inheritance of the Seven
Stars first: all of you, or me.
七星の遺産を
手に入れるかの勝負だ
賭け金は―
How about we wager
君たちの命でいかが？
all of your lives?
（将監）
ぐだぐだ うるせえんだよ！
Shut the hell up already!
（蓮太郎）速い！
He's fast!
（将監）ぶった斬れろやー！
I'll split you in two!
（将監）なっ!?
Wha...
（影胤）残念
Too bad...
下がれ 将監！
Fall back, Shogen!
あ… バリア… だと？
A barrier?
（影胤）斥力フィールドだ
It's a repulsion field.
私は“イマジナリーギミック”と
呼んでいる
I call it "Imaginary Gimmick."
（蓮太郎）お前 人間なのか？
Are you... human?
（影胤）もちろんだとも
Of course I am.
ただ これを発生させるために―
Though, to generate this,
内臓のほとんどを
バラニウムの機械に―
I've replaced most of my internal
organs with Varanium instruments.
詰め替えているがね
改めて名乗ろう 里見くん
Let me introduce myself properly, Satomi-kun.
私は 元陸上自衛隊東部方面隊―
I am formerly from the Ground
Self-Defense Force's Eastern Force,
７８７機械化特殊部隊
787th Mechanization Special Unit...
機械化!?
Mechanization?
（影胤）新人類創造計画
Hiruko Kagetane of the
New Humanity Creation Plan.
蛭子影胤
７８７…
787th... The Anti-Gastrea Special Unit?
対ガストレア用特殊部隊!?
実在するわけが…
There's no way that exists...
（影胤）信じる 信じないは
君たちの勝手だ
It's up to you whether you
choose to believe me or not.
フフフフッ ハハハハ…
はっ 木更さん！
Get down!
（一同）うわー！
（影胤）
フフフフフッ ハハハハ…
（影胤）里見くん
（蓮太郎）くっ
Satomi-kun.
（影胤）君にプレゼントだ
Here's a present for you.
行くよ 小比奈
Let's go, Kohina.
（小比奈）はい パパ
Okay, Papa.
（影胤）絶望したまえ 諸君
Despair, all of you. The day of extinction is nigh.
滅亡の日は近い
フフフフ…
里見くん
あの男と どこで会ったの？
Satomi-kun, where did you meet him?
それは…
Well...
（秘書）ううっ
た… 大変だ 社長が！
I-It's terrible! The President...
あれは 欠席してた
大瀬(おおせ)コーポレーションの秘書…
That's the secretary of the
President of Oose Corporation
who was absent...
しゃ… 社長が自宅で殺されて
Th-The President was killed in his home...
し… 死体の首がなくて
and the body's missing the head...
はっ
ああ…
うっ…
（聖天子）
新たな達成条件を加えます
I'm adding another
requirement for completion.
あの男より 先に
ケースを回収してください
Please recover the case before that man.
ケースの中身は
If its contents are misused,
悪用すれば
モノリスの結界を破壊し
it can destroy the Monolith barrier,
東京エリアに
〝大絶滅〞を引き起こす
and bring a great extinction
upon the Tokyo Area...
封印指定物です！
The contents are meant to be sealed away.
Tenchu Girls
♪（「天誅(てんちゅう)ガールズ」の
オープニング曲）
Seriously, what is this?
（蓮太郎）なんだよ これはよ…
That is a Tenchu Girls Bracelet
that is quite popular among us.
（藍原(あいはら)延珠）妾(わらわ)たちの間で大流行の
「天誅ガールズ」のブレスレットだ
If you deceive your friends or tell a lie,
仲間を欺いたり
ウソをついたりすると
it will crack and break apart.
ヒビが入って割れるのだ！
So why do I have this on?
それを なんで俺が…
For the couple's look!
（延珠）ペアルックだ！
Now you will not be able to deceive me.
これで 蓮太郎は
妾を欺くことはできんぞ！
If you were to be enchanted by
Kisara's boobies, it would break.
木更のおっぱいに見とれたりしても
割れてしまうからな
I, Satomi Rentaro, am in love with Aihara Enju.
私(わたくし) 里見蓮太郎は
藍原延珠のことを愛しています
It's not breaking.
フッ 割れねえな
That's because it's the truth.
真実だからだろう！
That's how you took it?
そうきたか…
イヒヒッ…
フッ
Damn...
クソッ…
It's like what happened yesterday was a lie...
まるで 昨日の出来事が
ウソみたいだ
Someone!
（男性）誰かー！
（延珠）あ…
Grab her!
（男性）そいつを捕まえろー！
（少女）ハァ ハァ ハァ…
あっ
（少女）ああっ
A Cursed Child from the Outer District...
（蓮太郎）
外周区の呪われた子供たち…
あ… あの… うわっ！
You thief!
（男性）この泥棒め！
（少女）放せー！
Let me go!
You're the trash of the Tokyo Area!
（男性）
貴様は 東京エリアのゴミだ！
Hey, why are you after her?
おい この子がどうして…
She stole something and then
（男性）盗みをやらかして―
almost killed the security
guard we called in response!
声をかけた警備員を
半殺しにしたんだ！
（男性）うっ…
（男性）この！
Why you...
Let me go!
（少女）放せ
ううっ…
あっ あ…
Let me go!
（少女）放せ…
What are you guys doing?!
（警官）貴様ら 何をやってる！
Please take care of this gir—
この子を保護してやって…
Come on! Hold still, you!
おら！ おとなしくしろ 貴様！
You don't even know what I did!
あたしが何をしたかも
知らないくせに！
フンッ お前らの
やりそうなことぐらい
I know exactly what your kind is likely to do!
全部 分かってる！
Hold still!
おとなしくしろ！
Come on, walk! Stop resisting!
（警官）ほら 歩くんだよ！
（警官）暴れるな
Quit flailing!
Be quiet!
（警官）静かにしろ！
（男性）外周区から出てくるな！
Don't ever leave the Outer District again!
（蓮太郎）フゥ…
Rentaro...
（延珠）蓮太郎…
Why didn't you save her?
なぜ 助けてやらなかった
You idiot! What are you doing?!
バカ 何やってんだ お前！
If they found out who
you were, you'd also be...
正体がバレたら お前まで…
But she was asking me for help!
妾に助けを求めていたのに！
Why...
なんで…
あ… まさか 知り合いなのか？
Did you know her?
Long ago, when I was in District 39,
昔 妾が39区にいたころ
I had seen her before...
見かけたことはある
Though I had never spoken to her...
ひと言も話したことは
なかったが―
She remembered me, as well.
あっちも妾を覚えていた！
Rentaro, you're a champion of justice!
蓮太郎は 正義の味方だ！
There's nothing that you can't do!
蓮太郎に
できないことなんてない！
Enju...
延珠…
Enju, you go on home.
延珠 先に帰ってろ
あ… えっ？
あっ
（蓮太郎）うっ
（延珠）あ…
Whoa!
（男性）うわっ
Why'd they bring her here?
（蓮太郎）なんで こんな所に？
（銃声）
あ…
She's still alive.
（警官）まだ生きてやがる
くっ…
Put us through all that damn effort...
（警官）手間かけさせやがって
Damn it... Why?!
（蓮太郎）
ちくしょう！ なんでだよ…
The ones protecting this city...
protecting all of you...
この街を…
お前たちを守ってんのは
are Cursed Children
この子と同じ―
just like her...
呪われた子供たちなんだぞ
And yet,
なのに 俺は… なんで！
why can't I...
はっ… ガハッ
（少女のせき込み）
She's alive!
生きてる！
She managed to survive somehow.
（医師）なんとか
一命を取り留めたよ
She's got quite the vitality.
すごい生命力だな
Thank you.
ありがとう
I'll pay for it, so please treat her properly.
カネは 俺が払うから
ちゃんと治療してやってくれ
You will? You sure?
あんたが？ 大丈夫かい？
Who else is going to pay?
（蓮太郎）
ほかに 誰が払ってくれるんだ？
（医師）ハァ…
（蓮太郎）ハァ…
Living expenses are going to be tight...
生活費 ヤベえな…
You seem tired, Satomi-kun...
（影胤）
お疲れのようだね 里見くん
Would you mind putting your gun down?
銃を下ろしてくれないかね？
I refuse!
断る！
（指を鳴らす音）
Kohina, cut off his right arm.
（影胤）小比奈 右腕を斬り落とせ
Yes, Papa.
はい パパ
Don't move, or your head will come off.
動かないで
首 落ちちゃう
フフッ
（延珠）はーっ！
I couldn't cut her...
斬れなかった
I couldn't kick her...
Oh?
（影胤）ほう
Hey, pipsqueak. Tell me your name.
そこのちっちゃいの 名前を教えて
You're small, too! How rude!
（延珠）お主だって
ちっちゃいだろ 無礼だな！
I am Aihara Enju, a Model Rabbit Initiator!
妾は藍原延珠
モデル･ラビットの
イニシエーターだ
Enju... I'll remember it.
延珠 覚えた
I am Model Mantis, Hiruko Kohina.
モデル･マンティス
蛭子小比奈
I am unrivaled in close range combat.
接近戦では 私は無敵！
I'll leave just that rabbit's head.
Can I cut her down?
あのウサギ 首だけにするから
斬っていい？
How many times must I tell
you, foolish daughter?
（影胤）何度も言ってるだろう
愚かな娘よ
No.
ダメだ
I hate you, Papa.
パパ 嫌い
Now, Satomi-kun, let me cut to the chase.
（影胤）さて 里見くん
単刀直入に言おう
Why not join forces with me?
私の仲間にならないか？
なん… だと？
What?
I'm not entirely sure why,
but I've taken a liking to you.
（影胤）最初から―
なぜだか 君のことが
好きになってしまってね
Have you
君は―
never once thought that the way things are
東京エリアの在り方は
間違っていると―
in the Tokyo Area is wrong?
そう思ったことは
一度もないかね？
（ケースを置く音）
あっ
This is a mere token, from me to you.
（影胤）私から ほんの気持ちだ
I heard that you're making
君は延珠ちゃんを―
Enju-chan act like a normal girl
and having her go to school.
普通の子供のフリをさせて
学校に通わせてるそうだね
（２人）あ…
Why would you do such a thing?
（影胤）なぜ そんなことをする？
They are the next generation of humanity
that have surpassed homo sapiens.
彼女たちは
ホモサピエンスを超えた―
次世代の人類だよ
Only ones with power like us will
survive the Great Extinction.
大絶滅のあと 生き残るのは
我々 力のある者たちだけだ
Side with me, Satomi Rentaro.
私につけ 里見蓮太郎！
（銃声）
I should have killed you the first time we met.
最初に会ったとき
貴様を殺しておけばよかったぜ
No matter how hard you work for them,
（影胤）君が いくら
ヤツらに奉仕したところで―
they will just continue to betray you.
ヤツらは 君を何度でも裏切る
（パトカーのサイレン）
Let's call it a day, Satomi-kun.
水入りだ 里見くん
Pay a visit to her school tomorrow,
明日 学校に行ってみるといい
and come face to face with reality.
現実を見るんだ
Rentaro... his Initiator is strong.
蓮太郎
あっちのイニシエーター 強いぞ
Can you beat her?
勝てるか？
I don't know.
分からない
I see...
（蓮太郎）そうか
（蓮太郎の荒い息遣い）
What do you mean?!
（蓮太郎）どういうことだよ！
A rumor that Aihara-san was one
of the Cursed Children suddenly
（担任）藍原さんが―
呪われた子供たちだという
ウワサが―
spread throughout the school...
校内で一気に広まってまして…
And Enju didn't deny it?
延珠は否定しなかったのか？
Satomi-san, you kept the
fact that Aihara-san was a
（担任）里見さん
あなた 藍原さんのことを
Cursed Child a secret from us, didn't you?
私たちに黙ってましたね
If I had told you upfront,
事前に言えば
wouldn't you have denied her
enrollment into the school?
あんたらは延珠の入学を
断ったんじゃねえのかよ？
Anyway, Aihara-san seemed
to take it as quite the shock,
（担任）とにかく 藍原さんは―
ショックを受けていたようなので
早退させました
so we sent her home early.
（ドアが開く音）
（蓮太郎）延珠！
Enju!
延珠！
（走る足音）
（延珠の鼻歌）
あっ
あ… おかえり 蓮太郎！
Welcome home, Rentaro!
What do you say? Care to join me?
どうだ？ 一緒に入らぬか？
Enju...
延珠…
Your home is here!
お前のうちは ここだろうが！
The New Gastrea Law is a law that will give
（聖天子）ガストレア新法は―
呪われた子供たちに
手にすべき人権を与える法案です
the Cursed Children the
rights that they deserve.
I am certain that this will
これは 必ずや―
serve as a foundation to a new
age that will come after the war.
大戦後の新たな時代の
礎となるでしょう
I believe it is my mission
since taking the position
この法案を契機に
人間同士の対立が消滅し―
of Seitenshi from my predecessor
to use the passing of this law
全ての人間が
融和できる社会へと―
39th District Map
You are here
as an opportunity to eliminate all fighting,
大きくかじを
取っていくことこそ―
and create a society where all
humans can live together in peace.
先代より聖天子の座を
受け継いだ―
私(わたくし)の使命だと考えます
What?
（マリア）何？
I'm a civil officer.
民警だ
I'm looking for this girl.
この子を捜してる
I don't know her.
知りません
I'd like to ask some other people, if possible.
ほかの人にも
聞いてみたいんだけど…
Okay, there's an Elder down here,
so please come wait inside.
じゃあ 長老おりますので
中でお待ちください
Elder!
（マリア）長老ー！
Are you the Elder?
（蓮太郎）あんたが長老か？
"Elder" is just a nickname.
（松崎(まつざき)）長老は愛称ですよ
松崎といいます
My name is Matsuzaki.
I take care of these children.
この子たちの面倒を見ています
In order for these girls to live
among normal people someday,
いずれ 普通の人々の中で
暮らすためにも―
I want to at least teach them
赤い目がバレないように―
how to control their emotions,
so their red eyes won't show.
感情を制御するすべは
最低限 学ばせたいのです
The Stolen Generation is cruel to them.
“奪われた世代”は
彼女たちに厳しい
If only everyone could think like you...
みんなが あんたみたいな
ものの考え方ができれば…
Did this girl come down here?
こいつが ここに来なかったか？
Sadly, I haven't seen her.
残念ながら知りませんな
I see...
（蓮太郎）そうか…
Where are you headed now?
これから どこへ？
I'm going to search all over the 39th District.
39区をくまなく…
It's her hometown, so I'm going
to look around until I find her.
こいつの故郷なんで
見つかるまで捜してみるよ
By the looks of it,
見たところ…
you're a Promoter whose partner ran out on you.
あなたは 相棒に逃げられた
プロモーターのようだ
Perhaps you could find another?
その子でなくとも よいのでは…
What?
何？
It's not uncommon that a civil
officer pair doesn't get along.
民警ペアの性格の不一致は
珍しいことではない
To many Promoters, Initiators are
mere tools used for fighting.
多くのプロモーターにとって
イニシエーターは
戦闘のための道具にすぎません
Tools?
（蓮太郎）道具!?
You could just contact the IISO and
（松崎）ＩＩＳＯに連絡して―
make a contract with a new Initiator.
新しいイニシエーターと
契約を結べばいい
You're a good man, and I'm grateful to you,
あんたは いいヤツで感謝もしてる
but...
でもな…
My reasons for looking for Enju have nothing
to do with Initiators or Promoters!
俺は イニシエーターだとか
プロモーターだとか
そんなの抜きで
延珠を捜しに来てるんだ！
The first time I met Enju was a year ago,
（蓮太郎）
最初に延珠と会ったのは １年前
when we were introduced
to each other at the IISO.
ＩＩＳＯで 引き合わされたときだ
Let's eat.
いただきます
うっ
Let's eat.
いただきまーす
We spent a lot of time
becoming more human together.
（蓮太郎）
俺たちは時間をかけて―
互いに 人間らしさを
身につけていった
For a year since then...
それから １年
We were always together, no matter what.
俺たちは―
どんなときも ずっと一緒だった
You don't know anything about us...
俺たちのことを
何も知らねえくせに
Stop talking like you understand everything!
偉そうに語んじゃねえよ！
Sorry...
悪い…
I didn't mean to yell.
どなるつもりじゃなかったんだ
I'll be leaving now.
もう行くよ
See ya.
じゃあな
He's a nice young man.
いい青年じゃないか
Are you sure you wanted to just
let him go like that, little girl?
このまま見送って
本当によかったのかい？
お嬢ちゃん
（延珠の泣き声）
♪～
～♪
#03 The Children of Fate
And yet we still have to fight...
（延珠）それでも 妾たちは―
Why must humanity exterminate the Gastrea?
戦わなければならないのか？
（室戸(むろと) 菫(すみれ)）人類は どうして―
Do you have any final words, dying people?
ガストレアを
せん滅しなければならない？
（影胤）
何か言い残すことは？
死にゆく友よ
If I don't stop them, the Tokyo Area will be...
（影胤）
何か言い残すことは？
死にゆく友よ
（影胤）
何か言い残すことは？
死にゆく友よ
（蓮太郎）
ヤツらを止められなければ
東京エリアは…
（蓮太郎）
ヤツらを止められなければ
東京エリアは…